I felt good and felt good, like when I took a bath.
お風呂に入ったときのような気持ちが良くて気持ちよくなってきて
There are, right?
いる んだよね
But it's long.
しかし、長いね
Like when I took a bath
お風呂に入ったときのような
I'm starting to feel better.
気 持ちが良くなってきているんだよね
Yes, I woke up.
はい、起きちゃった
debt
ふ
Uh huh
う ふう
Fuu ki
ふ う 気
It's disgusting, it's disgusting, it's like...
持 ち悪い 気持ち悪い おう おう なんか、
I'll try moving there.
そこで動いてみるよ
I'm sure
чем々 きっと
That's impossible.
あり えないよね
There are some really good cards.
すごくいいカードがあって
It's still in there, though.
入ってままだよ、でも
You're going to drink it yourself.
ペッチして飲みやがるでしょ、自分で
What, now?
何、今の?
That's right, as I turned around from the right side.
右側から振り向きながら、そうそう
It's a leg pin type, and it feels good.
足ピン系でしょ、気持ちいいと
move the bed
ベッドを動か
I'll do it.
して しまうね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
痛い、痛い、痛い
Have you gone?
行っちゃったの?
sorry.
ごめんなさい
The pussy is amazing.
おまんこすっごい
I don't like it.
嫌だ、
嫌 だ
It feels so good, it's getting closer.
感 覚よさ、近くなってんだね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I'll go again and again.
何度でも行くね
My pussy is so closed.
おまんこめちゃめちゃ閉まってるよ
Lie down for a moment with the fire.
火継いで、ちょっと横して